In the third assignment we're going to continue to further modify the index or
在这第三次大作业里 我们将继续修改
html file.
我们的 index.html 文件
There are four tasks in this assignment, and
我们一共需要完成四项任务
let me illustrate those four tasks to you by showing you the locations
现在我就来告诉你这四项任务
of those four tasks in the updated index.html page.
的详细内容
Going to your index.html page, the first task is to
进入到你的 index.html 页面 第一个任务就是
remove the tool tab from this button here so when you
把这个按钮上的工具提示去掉
put your mouse cursor on the button it will no longer show the tool tab.
所以当你将鼠标光标移到这个按钮上时 不会再有工具提示出现
Now, in bootstrap on a single element you cannot have multiple data attributes.
这是因为单个 Bootstrap 元素 不能含有多个数据属性
So which means that multiple JavaScript competence can't be invoked
也就是说 如果它含有多个数据属性的话
from a single element.
其中的任何一个都不会被调用
So that's why we have to remove the tool tab because I'm gonna be making use of
这就是为什么我们要将工具提示去掉
this button to invoke a model later on
因为接下来我们将用这个按钮
to show the reservation form for the table.
来调用出一个含有预约表格的模态框
The second task is to shift the reservation
而将我们之前实现过的位于 页面第四行的预约表格
form and the alert message that was there in the fourth
移植进一个模态框
content row on this page into a model.
就是我们的第二个任务
So as you can see, this model now contains the table
那么如图所示 就是一个含有 预约表格的模态框
reservation form here, and also the alert message has been moved into this model.
可以看到警告信息也被挪入了这个模态框
Now, to invoke this model, we are going to use
现在 我们需要用在超大屏幕中实现过的按钮
the reserve table button that we have already included in the Jumbotron.
来调用这个模态框
That is the third task for you.
而这就是我们的第三个任务
So, the third task is to setup the reserve table button so
那么再重复一遍 第三个任务
that when it is clicked the model will be shown on the screen.
就是用那个 Reserve Table 按钮来调用这个模态框
The last task of this assignment
至于最后一个任务
is to include another row here.
就是在这里加入另一行
In this row we will have a button group with two
在这一行里 我们需要加入两个单选按钮
radio buttons here which allows the user to
它们将允许用户选择预约餐厅中的
specify weather they want the non-smoking or the smoking section of the restaurant.
吸烟区还是非吸烟区
So this is a radio button group.
那么 这将是一个单选按钮组
By default, the non-smoking button is selected.
而且默认是选择非吸烟区
You can allow the user to select one or the other buttons,
你要允许用户选择且仅选择其中一个选项
so when one of the buttons is clicked, the other one should be deselected.
所以当其中一个按钮被选中时 另一个需要取消其被选中状态
The row should have the label name section and
这一行的标签是 Section
the Non-Smoking button should have green color, and
然后非吸烟区按钮的颜色需要是绿色的
the Smoking button should have red color.
吸烟区的则需要是红色的
Make use of Bootstrap's standard colors for configuring these two buttons there.
建议灵活运用 Bootstrap 的自带颜色来实现它
So this completes the third assignment.
以上 就是第三次大作业的全部内容 【翻译 - Carefree0910】